Squashed noses, scratched cheeks and t-shirts covered in sticky drinks.
被压扁的鼻子、被划伤的脸颊以及沾满黏糊糊饮料的T恤。
These are just some of the things that people are complaining about following the introduction of a new style of plastic bottle lid.
这些都是人们在新型塑料瓶盖推出后抱怨的一些事情。
Regulations in Europe now require manufacturers to tether lids to plastic drink bottles, making them difficult to remove.
欧洲的法规现在要求制造商将瓶盖连在塑料饮料瓶上，却使其难以取下。
Of course, the reason behind this measure is not to make people annoyed.
当然，推出这项措施的原因并不是为了让人们生气。
It's because when lids get separated from their bottles, they become a big problem.
而是因为当瓶盖与瓶子分离时，它们会成为一个大问题。
As they're small, bottle caps are easily discarded, representing a high percentage of the plastic waste found on beaches.
由于瓶盖很小，很容易被丢弃，在海滩上发现的塑料垃圾中占比很高。
UK surveys reported that bottle tops were the third most common type of waste found as litter.
英国的调查报告称，瓶盖是第三大最常见的垃圾类型。
They're more buoyant than bottles and so can travel further once they're in the sea.
它们比瓶子更具浮力，因此一旦进入海洋就能飘得更远。
They are then often mistaken for food by sea birds or other wildlife, endangering their health.
然后它们经常被海鸟或其他野生动物误认为是食物，危及它们的健康。
Wildlife photographer Chris Jordan, documented how Midway Atoll in the Pacific was covered with the bodies of thousands of seabirds whose stomachs were full of plastic pollution, much of it plastic bottle tops.
野生动物摄影师克里斯·乔丹记录了太平洋中途岛是如何被数千只海鸟的尸体覆盖的，这些鸟的胃里充满了塑料污染物，其中大部分是塑料瓶盖。
It's not just discarded lids that can be an issue.
不仅仅是丢弃的瓶盖会带来问题。
Carefully disposed of lids can present a problem in recycling plants.
被小心处理的瓶盖在回收厂也可能出现问题。
They are often too small for the machinery used to sort rubbish and end up being sent to landfill.
它们通常太小，无法被垃圾分类的机器处理，最终被送往垃圾填埋场。
Clever design could help reduce the scale of the problem.
巧妙的设计可以帮助减少问题。
The way products are built can influence our behaviour.
产品的制造方式可以影响我们的行为。
Consider a refrigerator that bleeps when left open too long.
想想冰箱，如果开门时间过长就会发出哔哔声。
The alarm encourages us to close the door, saving energy.
警报声促使我们关上门，从而节约能源。
Renee Wever, writing in the International Journal of Sustainable Engineering highlights how metal drink can ring pulls were redesigned in the 1980s, to remain attached to the cans.
雷内·韦弗在《国际可持续工程杂志》上撰文强调了20世纪80年代金属饮料罐的拉环是如何被重新设计的，使其保留在罐体上。
This is the approach which has been taken with plastic bottles.
人们现在将这种方法用于塑料瓶的生产。
If bottle tops are attached to bottles, they are more likely to be disposed of properly and less likely to present a problem to wildlife.
如果瓶盖与瓶子相连，它们就更有可能被妥善处理，对野生动物造成问题的可能性也更小。
Many recycling plants find it easier to recycle caps when they are attached to bottles.
许多回收厂发现，当瓶盖与瓶子相连时，更容易回收。
Could it be that making something slightly more difficult to use could make a real difference to solving our plastic waste problem.
也许，让某样东西使用起来稍微困难一点，就能真正帮助我们解决塑料垃圾问题。